

Adithyan Arun Kumar

OSCP | CEH (Master)

How to reach me:

Cell:

+91 7010951718

Email:

adithyan.ak@owasp.org

Website

adithyanak.com

Adress:

1/8, Thalambadi, Namakkal - 637019 India

Infosec Skills

- · Penetration testing
- Offensive Security
- Bug Bounty
- Exploit Development
- Malware Analysis
- · Security Research

CVE

- CVF-2019-6441
- CVE-2019-7562
- CVE-2019-7563
- CVE-2019-7564
- CVE-2019-7565

Education

B.Tech Information Technology

Aug 2017 - March 2021

Sri Krishna College of Engineering and Technology

Personal Profile

I'm an Offensive Security Researcher with 4+ years of research experience. I love to practice and preach Offensive Security

Programming Skills

- Python
- Bash
- (
- C++
- Java
- Django Framework

Career Summary

OWASP, Coimbatore — Chapter Head

July 2018 - Present

The role involves researching Application vulnerabilities and attack vectors, designing and developing open-source tools for application security, contributing to existing open-source projects in OWASP, and conducting cybersecurity awareness programs.

Gurugram Cyber cell, Haryana - Intern

May 2019 - June 2019

The internship includes researching real-world cybersecurity attacks against people, understanding cybersecurity laws, and developing security suites that can be used by Law Enforcement Agencies.

Stewards, London — QA Engineer (Remote Intern)

June 2019 - July 2019

The role revolves around testing the android application for performance-related issues, assessing security issues and risks present in the application, and proposing remedies to solve them.

Stewards, London — QA Engineer (Remote Intern)

Sept 2019 - Nov 2019

The role includes understanding threat analysis using a proprietary signature description language, troubleshooting, and testing IPS & Gateway AV engines on firmware, Researching new ways to improve the Deep Packet Inspection engine, Reverse engineering, and analyzing new malware threats.

Research & Achievements

- Top 10 Security Researcher Oppo Bug Bounty Leaderboard 2018.
- Winner at Hac'KP 2020 International Virtual Hackathon.
- Reverse Engineering and Backdooring Router Firmware IEEE International Conference on Advanced Computing and Communication Systems.
- LSAF: A Novel Comprehensive Application and Network Security
 Framework for Linux IEEE International Conference on Advanced
 Computing and Communication Systems.
- Remote Code Execution in Web Applications International Journal of Engineering and Technology
- Web Application Penetration Testing International Journal of Innovative Technology and Exploring Engineering (IJITEE)

Research & Achievements

WAVE — Web Application Vulnerability Scanner

A Python-based CLI tool that scans for web application vulnerabilities such as Cross-site scripting, SQL injection, local file inclusion, Host header injection, Clickjacking, and Cross-origin resource sharing.

OSINTsploit - Framework

A comprehensive OSINT framework built with Python that gathers information about a suspect through a variety of Open Source Intelligence techniques. Additional functionalities include metadata extraction, reverse image search, IP heat map creation, etc.

Track Their Download — REST API

An API built with Django REST Framework to display torrent download information of a given IPV4 address by scraping from an external source.

Covid-19 — Web Dashboard

A Django-based dynamic web application for displaying live statistical information about the infection status of the CoronaVirus [COVID-19].

Whatsapp Auto Chat Bot — ChatBot

An Artificially intelligent chatbot built with Python and selenium that can impersonate the user and speak to the user's selected WhatsApp contacts.

Certifications

- Offensive Security Certified Professional (OSCP)
- · Certified Ethical Hacker
- Certified Ethical Hacker Practical
- Certified Ethical Hacker (Master)

Hall Of Fame & Recognition

- Microsoft
- Oppo
- AT&T
- · Apple Security Advisory
- Intel
- Avira

Exploits

- www.exploitdb.com/exploits/46180
- www.exploitdb.com/exploits/46336

Authors Profiles

- Exploit-DB
- Cxsecurity
- Packetstormsecurity
- Vulmon
- Github
- Google Scholar

Social Handles

- Whatsapp
- LinkedIn
- Twitter
- Facebook

Character References

susila@skcet.ac.in Head of the Department, Information Technology, Sri Krishna College of Engineering and Technology

Dr. Sivabalan K N

knsbalan@skcet.ac.in Professor, Information Technology, Sri Krishna College of Engineering and Technology